<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Intertech LGBT+ Diversity Forum</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me</link><description>Founded in 2012, Intertech LGBT+ Diversity Forum (&#x201C;Intertech&#x201D;), is a community for LGBT+ individuals and their allies.

We encourage LGBT+ diversity and inclusion inthe UK technology sector for the benefit of the individual, the organisations they represent and the industry overall.</description><atom:link href="https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/77461</guid><title>Intertech @ GDS</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/77461</link><description>Join &lt;b&gt;Intertech LGBT+ Diversity Forum and the Government Digital Service (GDS)&lt;/b&gt; this Pride Month for an evening of insight and learning around how an organisation, whose job is the digital transformation of the Government, are truly &lt;b&gt;embracing innovation and driving positive change&lt;/b&gt;.

We'll hear from a number of speakers and see demonstrations of the technology behind GOV.UK Verify, their web platforms and much more - in addition we'll hear how &lt;b&gt;GDS are embracing diversity&lt;/b&gt; and the importance of this to them.

There'll also be a chance for networking and a &lt;b&gt;Mario Kart Tournament&lt;/b&gt; (Yes, you read that correctly...) afterwards, before in typical Intertech fashion we move to a nearby venue to continue the evening.

We look forward to seeing you there.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 17:35:38 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/77459</guid><title>Intertech @ Google Campus - LGBT+ Startup Networking</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/77459</link><description>We're delighted to invite you to join us for a &lt;b&gt;LGBT+ Startup networking event&lt;/b&gt; with Google Campus to meet like minded &lt;b&gt;entrepreneurs, makers and their supporters&lt;/b&gt; in this space.

Whether you identify as LGBT+, or simply wish to support the cause while enjoying an evening full of rainbows, we want everyone to join the celebration!

We really do want to make this evening as engaging and worthwhile for members who are&lt;b&gt; entreprenuers, working in start-ups, makers and investors&lt;/b&gt;, so if you do fit into one of these groups please sign-up as we'd love to see you there.

We're also delighted to have individuals from &lt;b&gt;Gayglers, Lesbians Who Tech and the Gay Womens Network&lt;/b&gt; joining us.

In typical fashion there will be drinks and nibbles, plus music and some amazing connections waiting for you on the evening - as well as post-event celebrations in a nearby venue.

See you there!</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 17:29:55 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76908</guid><title>Intertech @ Pride in London - Tickets Live Tomorrow!</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76908</link><description>Tickets for the&lt;b&gt; Intertech @ Pride in London 2018&lt;/b&gt; parade will be released tomorrow at 1230pm (noon).

If you'd like to join us on what promises to be our &lt;b&gt;biggest and brightest Pride in London&lt;/b&gt; so far then make sure you're online ready to sign-up using the link below.

&lt;a href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/intertech-pride-in-london-2018-tickets-46483504413"&gt;Register for Intertech @ Pride in London 2018 Parade&lt;/a&gt;

If you don't grab a ticket then please do join the waiting list as places will free up, plus we'll be running a raffle on the day for tickets that remain unclaimed - there's plenty of opportunity to get involved. We hope to see you there!

&lt;b&gt;Looking for our other events?&lt;/b&gt;

For all other planned events this month (GDS, Facebook &amp;amp; Palantir) these tickets will be released as normal, via email and social channels, as the month progresses to ensure that as many of our members can attend.</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 12:14:38 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76896</guid><title>VMware Sponsor Story - An Intertech sponsor...</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76896</link><description>With over 500,000 customers globally, VMware is the pioneer in virtualization and an innovator in cloud and business , they're also sponsoring Intertech LGBT+ Diversity Forum as one of our &lt;a href="https://prideinlondon.org/"&gt;Pride in London 2018&lt;/a&gt; sponsors. 

For more information on VMware visit their website or check out their social media using the links below:

&lt;a href="https://www.vmware.com/"&gt;Visit the VMware Website&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/VMware"&gt;Follow VMware on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 11:49:21 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76893</guid><title>TripAdvisor Sponsor Story - Marching proudly with Intertech once again...</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76893</link><description>Since 2016, TripAdvisor have supported Intertech with our Pride activities, and once again this year they'll be marching proudly with colleagues across the technology industry in London. It goes without saying, that they're also sponsoring Intertech LGBT+ Diversity Forum as one of our &lt;a href="https://prideinlondon.org/"&gt;Pride in London 2018&lt;/a&gt; sponsors. 

&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;We've asked them to share with you, our members, what diversity and inclusion means to TripAdvisor, and why they've chosen to work, once again, with us and support you all in celebrating Pride with Intertech this year...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

&lt;i&gt;'As the world's largest travel site*, TripAdvisor enables travellers to unleash the full potential of every trip. With over 630 million reviews and opinions covering the world's largest selection of travel listings worldwide &#x2013; covering approximately 7.5 million accommodations, airlines, experiences, and restaurants &#x2013; TripAdvisor provides travellers with the wisdom of the crowds to help them decide where to stay, how to fly, what to do and where to eat.'&lt;/i&gt;

This rather impressive intro to TripAdvisor, shows the real benefits that can be achieved when we stand together, and at TripAdvisor we were delighted to hear that they '&lt;i&gt;are deeply committed to our value of being "Better Together". We stand with our employees who are part of the LGBTQ+ community and are proud to support local participation in global Pride events.'&lt;/i&gt;

For the past few years, TripAdvisor teams have taken part in Pride parades around the world to show their pride and ally-ship. This year, we're looking forward to continuing the tradition TripAdvisor established in 2016 marching proudly with us and in their words &lt;i&gt;'We can't wait to celebrate with you all!'.&lt;/i&gt;

For more information on TripAdvisor visit their website or check out their social media using the links below:

&lt;a href="https://www.tripadvisor.com"&gt;Visit the TripAdvisor Website&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/TripAdvisor"&gt;Follow TripAdvisor on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;i&gt;*Source: comScore Media Metrix for TripAdvisor Sites, worldwide, October 2017&lt;/i&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 11:40:39 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76892</guid><title>Scott Logic Sponsor Story - A culture in which everyone is supported...</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76892</link><description>Scott Logic, the friendly people building brilliant software, are sponsoring Intertech LGBT+ Diversity Forum as one of our &lt;a href="https://prideinlondon.org/"&gt;Pride in London 2018&lt;/a&gt; sponsors. 

&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;We've asked them to share with you, our members, what diversity and inclusion means to Scott Logic, and why they've chosen to work with us and support you all in celebrating Pride with Intertech this year...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

&lt;i&gt;'At Scott Logic, we constantly strive to build an open and inclusive environment. As a people-focused technology consultancy, we pride ourselves on creating a culture in which everyone is supported to reach their full potential, whatever their background or identity. We are extremely pleased to be sponsoring Intertech for Pride in London 2018, and look forward to seeing you there!'&lt;/i&gt;

It's short and to the point but we're really looking forward to seeing Scott Logic there too!

For more information on Scott Logic visit their website or check out their social media using the links below:

&lt;a href="https://www.scottlogic.com/"&gt;Visit the Scott Logic Website&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/scott_logic"&gt;Follow Scott Logic on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 11:37:05 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76884</guid><title>Taylor Wessing Sponsor Story - Promoting LGBT equality and our culture of inclusion...</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76884</link><description>With over 1100 lawyers in 32 offices around the world, Taylor Wessing are a leading full-service international law firm, and an organisation that we're delighted are sponsoring Intertech LGBT+ Diversity Forum as one of our &lt;a href="https://prideinlondon.org/"&gt;Pride in London 2018&lt;/a&gt; sponsors. 

&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;We've asked them to share with you, our members, what diversity and inclusion means to Taylor Wessing, and why they've chosen to work with us and support you all in celebrating Pride with Intertech this year...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

&lt;i&gt;'Creating an inclusive working environment and recognising the value our people bring to Taylor Wessing is at the heart of our culture; it's what makes Taylor Wessing a great place to work.&lt;/i&gt;' is a rather perfect way of explaining why Taylor Wessing has committed to sponsoring Intertech and why we're so pleased to have them join us at Pride in London 2018. 

As an orgasniation '&lt;i&gt;working with clients in the most dynamic industries helping them succeed by thinking innovatively about their business issues&lt;/i&gt;' their '&lt;i&gt;focus on the industries of tomorrow has enabled them to develop market-leading expertise in Life Sciences, Private Wealth and Technology, Media and Communications&lt;/i&gt;', but this hasn't stopped them pushing forwards in ensuring that diversity and inclusion remain core to their business, as the following illustrates.

As a &lt;a href="https://www.stonewall.org.uk/full-list-top-100-employers-2018"&gt;Stonewall Top 100 employer&lt;/a&gt;, Taylor Wessing clearly champion LGBT+ inclusion and have therefore become a market leader in diversity initiatives. When we asked them why Intertech? They told us, '&lt;i&gt;We are proud to sponsor Intertech at Pride London 2018. Technology is one of the youngest and yet, one of the fastest growing sectors. Our support represents our shared values and our commitment to improving LGBT equality.'&lt;/i&gt;

We were also lucky to hear directly from Sian Skelton, Diversity &amp; Inclusion Partner, who stated,'&lt;i&gt;We are committed to promoting LGBT equality and our culture of inclusion to extend beyond the firm to the wider community. As Diversity &amp; Inclusion Partner, and a tech lawyer, I am delighted that we are sponsoring Intertech at Pride this year.'&lt;/i&gt;

If all of the above doesn't paint a picture of just how supportive Taylor Wessing are both of Intertech, the LGBT+ community and of ensuring diversity and inclusion remains a constant stream in their business; then we're not sure what else would...

For more information on Taylor Wessing visit their website or check out their social media using the links below:

&lt;a href="https://united-kingdom.taylorwessing.com/"&gt;Visit the Taylor Wessing Website&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/taylorwessinguk"&gt;Follow Taylor Wessing on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 11:23:21 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76882</guid><title>myGwork Sponsor Story - Together, we are empowered!</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76882</link><description>myGwork, the global LGBT+ social recruitment platform will be joining us to march in this years Pride in London parade. They are also very kindly sponsoring Intertech LGBT+ Diversity Forum as one of our &lt;a href="https://prideinlondon.org/"&gt;Pride in London 2018&lt;/a&gt; sponsors. 

&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;As an organisation built around championing diversity, we know they're really passionate about diversity and inclusion, but we still went ahead and asked them to share with you, our members, what diversity inclusion means to myGwork and why they've chosen to work with us and support you all in celebrating Pride with Intertech this year...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

myGwork, the LGBT+ and allies business community, is the global LGBT+ social recruitment platform that helps candidates identify inclusive employers, network, find mentors, learn about professional LGBT+ news, and engage in LGBT+ &amp; D&amp;I events. You can check out their promotional video &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7hI_-ZvXSA8&amp;t=5s"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.

For that reason, they told us that they '&lt;i&gt;want to contribute to building a global workforce that champions diverse organisations and give better employment &amp; networking opportunities to the LGBT+ community. As an LGBT+ tech company, we are very excited to support Intertech and march together at Pride in London 2018. Together, we are empowered!'&lt;/i&gt;

We're delighted to have myGwork on board - they're an organisation with a string of awards and accolades, with their founders being named as 'Attitude Award Young LGBT Entrepreneur of the Year 2016' and 'Financial Time #38 Top Future LGBT Leaders'

For more information on myGwork visit their website or check out their social media using the links below:

&lt;a href="https://www.mygwork.com/"&gt;Visit the myGwork Website&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/mygwork"&gt;Follow myGwork on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 11:11:27 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76865</guid><title>Softwire Sponsor Story - A great place to work for everyone...</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76865</link><description>Softwire are sponsoring Intertech LGBT+ Diversity Forum as one of our &lt;a href="https://prideinlondon.org/"&gt;Pride in London 2018&lt;/a&gt; sponsors. 

&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;We've therefore asked them to share with you, our members, what diversity inclusion means to Softwire and why they've chosen to work with us and support you all in celebrating Pride with Intertech this year...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Softwire is a London based software development company delivering bespoke software solutions and applications for some of the UK&#x2019;s leading brands, and they were delighted to share with us why they truly do value '&lt;i&gt;a diverse workforce and the contribution each individual makes&lt;/i&gt;'. 

Just like the objectives of Intertech, they are committed to promoting inclusivity, equality and diversity in their policies, practices and procedures, and to '&lt;i&gt;ensuring that no one feels left out as they work hard to create an inclusive working environment which allows people to simply be themselves at work&lt;/i&gt;'

It goes without saying that Softwire believes in treating everyone equally and with the same attention, courtesy and respect, and that diverse and inclusive companies make for more innovative, engaged, and happy teams. &lt;i&gt;'Softwire is a great place to work for everyone, this has been reflected in our position in the top &lt;a href="https://appointments.thetimes.co.uk/article/best100companies/"&gt;25 Sunday Times Best Small Companies&lt;/a&gt; for the past 8 years.'&lt;/i&gt;

We know that we're looking forward to marching with Softwire this year and having heard about the vibrant social scene and numerous LGBT+ themed events that they host we're sure it'll be a carnival atmosphere. 

For more information on Softwire visit their website or check out their social media using the links below:

&lt;a href="https://www.softwire.com/"&gt;Visit the Softwire Website&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/SoftwireUK"&gt;Follow Softwire on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 10:41:45 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76859</guid><title>Capco Sponsor Story - A long standing supporter...</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76859</link><description>One of our long standing supporters and an organisation that is close to our hearts, Capco are sponsoring Intertech LGBT+ Diversity Forum as one of our &lt;a href="https://prideinlondon.org/"&gt;Pride in London 2018&lt;/a&gt; sponsors. 

&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;We know they're an organisation truly embracing what it means to support diversity and inclusion, but we still wanted to share with you, our members, what diversity and inclusion means at Capco, and why they're supporting you all in celebrating Pride with Intertech this year...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Capco has a very strong relationship with Intertech having co-hosted a number of events in the past and being truly proud to support LGBTQ+ members in the industry. 

As a global business and technology consultancy focused on financial services, they believe that '&lt;i&gt;true inclusion is about fostering an environment where all employees can be themselves at work' &lt;/i&gt;and their &lt;a href="https://www.capco.com/About-Us/Our-Culture-and-Values/Be-yourself-at-work"&gt;#BeYourselfAtWork networks&lt;/a&gt;, sponsored by the firm, are an integral part of their culture and progress on diversity.

On daily basis, they told us that they celebrate individuality and believe:

&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;everyone should be proud of and open about who they are, and challenge stereotypes;

&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;everyone has a right at be safe at work, and to bring their whole self to work;

&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;i&gt;everyone has the opportunity to mix and celebrate what they have in common as well as their differences.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;We simply couldn't agree more... and we're so pleased that Capco will join us once again this year to further demonstrate their visible commitment to diversity and inclusion.

For more information on Capco visit their website or check out their social media using the links below:

&lt;a href="https://www.capco.com/"&gt;Visit the Capco Website&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Capco"&gt;Follow Capco on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 10:32:08 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76847</guid><title>Kemp Little Sponsor Story - Proud to share our values around diversity and inclusion...</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76847</link><description>It's a first! Kemp Little are marching in Pride in London for the very first time with us, and if that wasn't enough of a reason to celebrate they've also sponsored Intertech LGBT+ Diversity Forum as one of our &lt;a href="https://prideinlondon.org/"&gt;Pride in London 2018&lt;/a&gt; sponsors. 

&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;We wanted to find out just how excited they are about this, as well gain a little more insight to share with you, our members, about what diversity and inclusion means at Kemp Little. Plus, why they've chosen to work with us, whilst support you all in celebrating Pride with Intertech this year...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

&lt;i&gt;'Kemp Little started out as a specialist tech law firm and 21 years later we are still at our core a tech-focused and tech-driven firm. We are the go-to specialists for companies across the board who are reliant on technology for their success from start-ups, to unicorns to FTSE 100 names. We are also proud signatories of the &lt;a href="https://www.lawsociety.org.uk/support-services/practice-management/diversity-inclusion/diversity-inclusion-charter/"&gt;Law Society&#x2019;s Diversity and Inclusion Charter&lt;/a&gt; and work hard to embed and live its values in the way we work and recruit and the way we relate to one another.&lt;/i&gt;

&lt;i&gt;This is the first year that Kemp Little has marched at Pride with Intertech and we are excited to be partnering with an organisation which not only shares our values around diversity and inclusion, but which is also centred around tech companies, which is the sector at the heart of Kemp Little&#x2019;s evolution.'&lt;/i&gt;

We don't think we could've worded that any better, so we didn't, but we can be sure that Kemp Little are going to bring some some real excitement and atmosphere to the day.

For more information on Kemp Little visit their website or check out their social media using the links below:

&lt;a href="http://www.kemplittle.com/"&gt;Visit the Kemp Little Website&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/KempLittle"&gt;Follow Kemp Little on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 10:18:48 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76846</guid><title>Simply Business Sponsor Story - Profitability is equally important as impact on society...</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76846</link><description>Simply Business, the UK's biggest business insurance broker, are sponsoring Intertech LGBT+ Diversity Forum as one of our &lt;a href="https://prideinlondon.org/"&gt;Pride in London 2018&lt;/a&gt; sponsors. 

&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;We wanted to get to know them a little more so we asked them to share with you, our members, what diversity inclusion means at Simply Business and why they've chosen to work with us, whilst support you all in celebrating Pride with Intertech this year...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Twice named as The Sunday Times Best Company to Work For and recognised as an accredited B Corporation, Simply Business is a tech driven insurance company working to create the best possible insurance experience for small businesses and self-employed people - whilst at the same time ensuring diversity and inclusion remain at the top of their agenda.

We asked Simply Business to give us a quick insight into how they've managed this...

&lt;i&gt;'We&#x2019;re one of the UK&#x2019;s biggest providers of business insurance, trusted by over 425,000 customers. With over 400 employees across two UK offices - and a growing US team in Boston. We believe that business should be a force for good. Profitability is important &#x2013; and being successful gives us the opportunity to make a bigger impact &#x2013; but having a positive impact on society and the environment is equally important.'&lt;/i&gt;

&lt;i&gt;'From improving the lives of our employees and creating a better future through our charity work, to ensuring we don&#x2019;t harm our environment, we have a proven track record of taking our social responsibility seriously, both for our workers and the wider community.'&lt;/i&gt;

So as you can see, they really are, as a business, '&lt;i&gt;fundamentally committed to supporting anyone who falls under the LGBTQ+ umbrella, and we&#x2019;re honoured to march with Intertech at Pride in London this year.' &lt;/i&gt;We should say we're also honoured to have Simply Business join us for what promises to be our biggest Pride yet!

For more information on Simply Business visit their website or check out their social media using the links below:

&lt;a href="https://www.simplybusiness.co.uk/"&gt;Visit the Simply Business Website&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/simplybusiness"&gt;Follow Simply Business on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 10:04:39 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76845</guid><title>Capgemini Sponsor Story - Enabling everyone to bring themselves to work...</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76845</link><description>We were so excited to announce that Capgemini, having supported us in a number of ways of the last few years, are sponsoring Intertech LGBT+ Diversity Forum as one of our &lt;a href="https://prideinlondon.org/"&gt;Pride in London 2018&lt;/a&gt; sponsors. 

&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;We wanted to therefore ask them to share with you, our members, what diversity inclusion means at Capgemini and why they've chosen to work with us, whilst support you all in celebrating Pride with Intertech this year...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;

Capgemini run an established diversity and inclusion programme and for that reason they were '&lt;i&gt;delighted to support Intertech' as this relationship is an important element within our intersectional Active Inclusion programme&lt;/i&gt;'. This year they've taken great steps in entering &lt;a href="https://www.stonewall.org.uk/full-list-top-100-employers-2018"&gt;Stonewall&#x2019;s Top 100 Employers&lt;/a&gt; and in their words '&lt;i&gt;supporting Intertech at Pride in London is a visible part of our commitment in continuing our work to enable everyone to bring themselves to work&lt;/i&gt;'. 

Here at Intertech, and at many of the organisation we work with, we all know that the business benefits of a diverse and inclusive workforce speak for themselves. However, at Capgemini they're so proud to be a Stonewall Top 100 Employer and Stonewall Diversity Champion as they really understand that this enables them to continue to work '&lt;i&gt;to create an inclusive, safe and supportive workplace environment for all of our employees&lt;/i&gt;.' It's really amazing stuff!

Their LGBT+ and Allies network, &lt;a href="https://www.capgemini.com/gb-en/careers/life-at-capgemini/respect-for-diversity/outfront-our-capgemini-uk-lgbt-employee-network/"&gt;OUTfront&lt;/a&gt;, supports their Active Inclusion ethos and they told us that &lt;i&gt;'this is all part of ensuring that as a business they drive an organisation that is more inclusive and better equipped to support colleagues and clients in an increasingly diverse global marketplace.'&lt;/i&gt;

We're really looking forward to marching together with Capgemini, it&#x2019;s a highlight of the LGBT+ calendar in the UK and a vibrant day of freedom, individuality, pride, protest and celebration.'

We can't wait! 

For more information on Capgemini visit their website or check out their social media using the links below:

&lt;a href="https://www.capgemini.com/"&gt;Visit the Capgemini Website&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/CapgeminiUK"&gt;Follow Capgemini on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 10:02:49 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76778</guid><title>Nutmeg Sponsor Story - Business should reflect our customers and our community...</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/76778</link><description>After an incredible event with &lt;a href="https://www.nutmeg.com"&gt;Nutmeg&lt;/a&gt; just over a month ago, we were delighted to hear that they were keen to continue to support Intertech LGBT+ Diversity Forum as one of our &lt;a href="https://prideinlondon.org/"&gt;Pride in London 2018&lt;/a&gt; sponsors. 

&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;We've therefore asked them to share with you, our members, what diversity inclusion means to Nutmeg and why they've chosen to work with us and support you all in celebrating Pride with Intertech this year...&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;

Nutmeg operates in an industry that has traditionally been regarded as not being very diverse at all, yet here at Intertech we were delighted to hear that&lt;i&gt; 'diversity and inclusion are essential values at Nutmeg' &lt;/i&gt;and that they truly 'believe that their business should reflect their customers and community'. 

We were also incredibly impressed to learn that Nutmeg are also signed up to the &lt;a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/women-in-finance-charter"&gt;Women in Finance Charter&lt;/a&gt; and are Stonewall Diversity Champions. Their CEO, Martin Stead, whom spoke passionately at our &lt;a href="https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/68905"&gt;Intertech @ Nutmeg&lt;/a&gt; event, is also named on the OUTstanding LGBT+ Executive 2017 list in recognition of his passionate advocacy of workplace equality and diversity.

Nutmeg told us that '&lt;i&gt;supporting Intertech fits with Nutmeg&#x2019;s commitment to diversity and inclusion as a key part of the way we do business&lt;/i&gt;' and that marching with us for 'P&lt;i&gt;ride in London 2018 helps us celebrate the values we live by as a business&lt;/i&gt;'.

We're so excited to be joined by friends from an organisation that is doing so much for promoting and encouraging diversity whilst clearly having a great time doing so too.

For more information on Nutmeg visit their website or check out their social media using the links below:

&lt;a href="https://www.nutmeg.com/"&gt;Visit the Nutmeg Website&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/thenutmegteam"&gt;Follow Nutmeg on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 01:36:48 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/75517</guid><title>A MASSIVE Thank You for our Pride 2018 Sponsors!!! &#x1F389;&#x1F389;&#x1F389;</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/75517</link><description>This year we are very excited to be working with a 11 sponsors (!) who have been tremendously generous in supporting Intertech @ Pride this year. You&#x2019;ll hear more about these wonderful folks over the coming weeks!</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 15:58:41 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/75516</guid><title>BRACE YOURSELVES - PRIDE IS HERE</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/75516</link><description>To celebrate the first day of Pride Month 2018, we are PROUD and ECSTATIC to share our &lt;a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/11kySDxPH40bf7enoYv_X6gVjDRw7rj9t/view?usp=sharing"&gt;Pride Calendar&lt;/a&gt; which includes all the exciting events which are happening between now and the Pride in London march on the 7th of July &#x1F603;&#x1F389;&#x1F603;&#x1F389;&#x1F603;&#x1F389;&#x1F603;&#x1F389;

&lt;b&gt;EVENTS:&lt;/b&gt;

In the last 3 months, a super secret team of Intertech heroes and heroines have helped to organise 5 absolutely fantastic events which we&#x2019;re certain will get you in the mood for what we hope to be Intertech's BEST PRIDE EVER! 

Due to unprecedented popularity the first 2 events - have already been fully booked, so please make sure you look out for more comms over the next few weeks.

5th June - Microsoft - FULLY BOOKED

12th June - Deliveroo - FULLY BOOKED

28th June - Government Digital Service

4th July - Facebook

5th July - Palantir

&lt;b&gt;PRIDE:&lt;/b&gt;

This year will be bigger and better than ever with an expanded ticket allocation and loads of swag! To ensure that ticket distribution is fair, we will be releasing these over 2 days - the first in the evening and the second during lunch time. When selecting your ticket, please can you also ensure that you select your T-shirt size &#x1F455;

Ticket Release 1: Wednesday 6th June 7:00pm

Ticket Release 2: Friday 8th June 12:30pm

&lt;b&gt;What if I missed out on a ticket? &#x1F628;&lt;/b&gt;

We anticipate that Pride tickets will be very popular, however fear not! Sign up for our waitlist on the second ticket release and we will keep you in the loop about our Pride activities. On the day of Pride, if you are planning to visit London and would like the chance to join the parade, please bring your wonderful self and your waitlist ticket to our parade meeting point for the chance to win tickets from no-shows in our raffle! We will try and match you with your T-shirt size but unfortunately this cannot be guaranteed - whatever size of T-shirt, we are sure that something &#x1F984;FABULOUS &#x1F984; can be created from it!</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 15:41:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/75000</guid><title>Intertech @ Microsoft GLEAM - Pre-Pride Kickoff</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/75000</link><description>Intertech &amp; Microsoft invite you to a &lt;b&gt;special networking (+ ping-pong!)&lt;/b&gt; evening as we start to get ready for Pride in London season.

We have secured a private room at Bounce Farringdon (nearest tube: Chancery Lane) where we'll have exclusive use of the ping-pong tables in this room and &lt;b&gt;a limited free bar&lt;/b&gt;! 

We'll have a brief hello from the Microsoft Diversity team who will share some of their plans for the year with us, then there'll be plenty of time for networking, while our Bounce ping-pong gurus bring out our competitive sides!

&lt;b&gt;Microsoft Employee, Customer or Friend?&lt;/b&gt;

If you're a Microsoft employee, vendor or otherwise affiliated with Microsoft then please use the following link to register for this event http://aka.ms/pride-kickoff</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 09:57:39 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/73754</guid><title>Intertech @ Deliveroo</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/73754</link><description>We are excited to announce the next Intertech event in association with Deliveroo, to celebrate the start of Pride month. Join us on Deliveroo&#x2019;s own basketball court for an evening of short talks and panel discussions.

&lt;b&gt;Short talks&lt;/b&gt;

Three members of the Deliveroo tech team will take to the Roopitch to give short talks on topics ranging from &lt;em&gt;Diversity of personalities&lt;/em&gt; to &lt;em&gt;How do you ask a machine a question?&lt;/em&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Panel&lt;/b&gt;

&lt;em&gt;Diversity: inclusive or exclusive?&lt;/em&gt;

Next there will be a discussion with representatives from Deliveroo, Stonewall and Lloyds Bank around whether having specific diversity groups within a business actually promotes an inclusive, or exclusive culture.

&lt;b&gt;Food &amp;amp; Drink&lt;/b&gt;

In true Deliveroo style, plenty of food and drink (including alcohol free options) will be provided! If you have specific dietary requirements, please specify these when signing up.

&lt;b&gt;Register&lt;/b&gt;

Please register for the event at the link below. If you register but are unable to make the event, then please do cancel your ticket as there are limited spaces!

You will need to sign an NDA on arrival. To speed up the process we&#x2019;ve provided a copy for you to read in advance at this &lt;a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/16ec4Ig7FugGt2QM174UPLE0_JHuneo1b/view" title="Deliveroo NDA" target="_blank" data-mce-href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/16ec4Ig7FugGt2QM174UPLE0_JHuneo1b/view"&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 09:41:15 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/68905</guid><title>Intertech @ Nutmeg</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/68905</link><description>Nutmeg is inviting Intertech members to their Vauxhall offices for a night of tech, diversity, fun and frivolity (aligned to your risk profile) - but don't worry, your capital is not at risk by attending this event!

We'll be hearing from three speakers on the topics of how immersive technologies are transforming our lives, why even your best ideas might not be actually that great, and of course we'll get an insight into how Nutmeg is using technology to transform it's business and engage with it's users.

Speakers on the evening will be:

Martin Stead, CEO of Nutmeg

Tom Hewitson, CEO of Labworks.io

Mark Stringer, Partner at Capco

Casey Lord, Product Manager at Nutmeg

We look forward to seeing you at what promises to be another great evening.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 10:27:26 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/66182</guid><title>Intertech @ MPC - Software development in VFX</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/66182</link><description>Join us for an engaging evening with MPC (Moving Picture Company) looking at the vital role of &lt;b&gt;Software Development in the VFX industry.&lt;/b&gt; We'll be hearing from Rob Pieke, &lt;b&gt;Head of New Technology&lt;/b&gt;, who will guide us through his experiences, insight and of course present some of MPC's award winning work.

Rob's talk will be following be a &lt;b&gt;Q&amp;amp;A session and network opportunities&lt;/b&gt; over drinks before in typical Intertech fashion moving on to a nearby venue to continue the evening.

Please be advised that &lt;b&gt;strictly no photography&lt;/b&gt; will be permitted on the evening and by signing up to this event you agree to be covered by a non-disclosure agreement between Intertech &amp;amp; MPC. 

We look forward to seeing you at what promises to be a fantastic evening.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 09:46:13 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/66179</guid><title>Intertech @ Comedy Bloopers - A Night of Gay Comedy</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/66179</link><description>&lt;b&gt;What do you call a sheep with no legs? A cloud...&lt;/b&gt;

For jokes better than this and an evening jam packed with laugh out loud funniness, join us at the &lt;b&gt;New Bloomsbury Set &lt;/b&gt;on Wednesday evening courtesy of Comedy Bloomers, a diverse group of &lt;b&gt;LGBT+ comedians&lt;/b&gt; who host regular stand up comedy nights throughout the year!

We've already over a &lt;b&gt;100 of you signed up to come along&lt;/b&gt; so we're looking forward to a fantastic evening, further more tickets are available all the way up to the day of the event so if you find yourself free on the night, just sign up and come along.

&lt;i&gt;(...and if you are coming the venue is down the steps next to the little green door).&lt;/i&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 09:07:23 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/66177</guid><title>Intertech @ Pride in London - We need you!</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/66177</link><description>The &lt;b&gt;Pride in London Parade&lt;/b&gt; is held annually to celebrate progress made in the LGBT+ community towards equality and remind us of the of the ongoing LGBT+ issues not just in London but all over the world. 

This year, Intertech will once again be joining in the festivities with a "SHEDLOAD"(technical term) of events from our sponsors, on the day activities and more Intertech members marching than before.

&lt;b&gt;Intertech Pride 2018 promises to be the bigger and better than ever before!&lt;/b&gt;

Over the coming months, we will be sharing more details, however for now we need some key support from the Intertech community to help make this happen. This will include low key activities (i.e. attending weekly calls, taking a few actions) and potentially on the day tasks to help the day run smoothly. We respect the time and capacity of our volunteers so we'll &lt;b&gt;guarantee you a marching ticket&lt;/b&gt; to say thank you.

If you are interested in helping out over the coming months, please drop jerr2y.chen@gmail.com or rfarthing@outlook.com an email and we will take it from there!</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 05:02:29 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/60103</guid><title>Intertech @ Midrive - How to build a multi-million pound marketplace</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/60103</link><description>Join us for an evening of conversation, questions and insight with &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="http://midrive.com/" target="_blank" data-mce-href="http://midrive.com/"&gt;Midrive&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;and &lt;a href="http://crowdcube.com/" target="_blank" data-mce-href="http://crowdcube.com/"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Crowdcube&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; considering how both businesses have scaled from small tech start-ups to successful multi-million pound marketplaces.

We'll be hearing from Asher Ismail, Midrive CEO (and Intertech royalty, having co-founded Intertech in 2012).

In the last 12 months, sales of Midrive&#x2019;s &#x2018;smarter lessons&#x2019; and &#x2018;pay as you go&#x2019; insurance have increased 391%. Asher will be sharing his&lt;b&gt; top lessons&lt;/b&gt; for scaling a marketplace business (and the necessary technology), with examples from Uber, eBay, and AirBnb, as well as some mistakes he's made along the way as an entrepreneur.

We'll also be joined by Darren Mulvihill of Crowdcube who will share the challenges they have overcome in creating the &lt;b&gt;UK&#x2019;s largest crowdfunding marketplace&lt;/b&gt;.

In typical Intertech fashion, drinks and canap&#xE9;s will be provided and we'll continue the evening, and conversation, in a nearby venue afterwards.

See you there,

Intertech Team

&lt;em&gt;P.S. Midrive is running a live &#xA3;1.8m equity crowdfunding campaign on Crowdcube, &lt;a href="http://www.crowdcube.com/midrive" target="_blank" data-mce-href="http://www.crowdcube.com/midrive"&gt;check it out here&lt;/a&gt;. You can get involved from as little as &#xA3;10. #capitalatrisk&lt;/em&gt;

&lt;em&gt;

&lt;/em&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 14:00:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/58327</guid><title>Intertech @ Starling Bank - A celebration of IWD and Diversity in Technology &amp; Finance</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/58327</link><description>In celebration of &lt;b&gt;Women's History Month&lt;/b&gt;, Starling Bank and Intertech invite our members to join Starling Bank at their office to gain an insight into one of London&#x2019;s &lt;b&gt;HOTTEST Fintech start ups&lt;/b&gt;! 

Learn more about Starling Bank's tech and app, as well as how they're &lt;b&gt;embracing diversity and women in technology&lt;/b&gt;. This will be followed by a brief, informal and jovial discussion with Starling Bank where you're invited to ask all your burning questions. 

Food and drinks will be provided with vegetarian and non-alcoholic beverages too. 

Plus, if you fancy joining us a little later in the evening, we will be in a local watering hole after 9pm so feel free to join us then!</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 23:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/55845</guid><title>'Twas the night before Friday - Intertech Social @ Yard Bar - No Tickets Required!</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/55845</link><description>&lt;i&gt;"Twas the night before Friday, when all through the office,

Not a person was working, not even Doris.

Where are they you ask, where can they be?

At the Intertech March Social of course! Where you should be!"&lt;/i&gt;

Original work by Jerry Chen and coming to a GCSE English Literature anthology near you! Doris normally works very long hours but on Thursdays, she lets her hair down. 

You're invited to come an &lt;b&gt;join us and many more Intertech members&lt;/b&gt; at Yard Bar in Soho and let your hair down with a drink (alcoholic or not!).

NO TICKETS OR SIGN-UP REQUIRED! :D</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 23:59:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/55678</guid><title>A Celebration of LGBTQ and Allies in Fintech</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/55678</link><description>In celebration of &lt;b&gt;LGBT History Month and Black History Month&lt;/b&gt;, an active Intertech Member Nzube Ufodike has organised this panel and networking event in collaboration with DueDil, the private company information platform, and has invited all of Intertech to join! 

The ticket price is &#xA3;5 and all proceeds go to the &lt;b&gt;Albert Kennedy Trust&lt;/b&gt;, whose mission is to prevent LGBT youth homelessness through safe home and advocacy.

The event takes place on Feb 27th from 6-9pm with the event partners Duedil &amp;amp; Intertech.

We've confirmed an exciting panel and keynote on the topic of&lt;b&gt; 'Celebrating LGBT (+ Allies) in Fintech'. &lt;/b&gt;You can sign-up and find out more on the Eventbrite page below.

You are welcome to share this with your networks. I look forward to seeing you there.

Contact Nzube Ufodike on 07830143489 or email at nzube@amoo.co.uk</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 12:43:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/52272</guid><title>Intertech @ Capco - What's hot and what's not in 2018...</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/52272</link><description>Join us on Thurs 8th Feb to &lt;b&gt;kick-off the new year&lt;/b&gt; with a rundown on what's on the horizon for Intertech, our members and the ever changing tech sector that we live and work in.

With the topic of &lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;'What's hot and what's not in 2018...'&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; we've pulled together a real spectrum of speakers who are eager to give their insight and opinions. 

Furthermore, we're inviting any of you to take to also take to the floor for a few informal minutes and tell us &lt;b&gt;what has got you excited for the year ahead?&lt;/b&gt; Be it something you're working on, something you've seen or maybe just a hunch. Simply sign-up to attend as normal but also check the 'I've got something to share!' option if you want to contribute.

We're also delighted to once again be hosted by our friends over at &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.capco.com/"&gt;Capco&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;/b&gt;who have very generously ensured that &lt;b&gt;drinks and pizza&lt;/b&gt; will be in ample supply, and in typical Intertech fashion we'll extend an invite to all attending to join us afterwards in a venue to be confirmed.

So sign-up now for what promises to be an evening full of &lt;b&gt;insight, opportunity and a fantastic chance to catch-up&lt;/b&gt; with your fellow Intertech members.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 20:25:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/44281</guid><title>InterTech Social</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/44281</link><description>Our last social event of 2017 will be held at the Big Chill Bar! Come and join us for one (or many) final beer(s) before people escape London for Christmas :)

It has been a whirlwind of a year for InterTech and we're so proud to be part of such a wonderful community. 

This year we have had some amazing events with some incredible partners including BCG, Visa, Microsoft, Imagination, Palantir, Google, Salesforce, The Institute of Directors, Capgemini, Capco, Goldman Sachs, Mozilla and BBC News! 

Together, we have created an amazing buzz around InterTech and we're really getting noticed across the London tech community! We have received a lot of interest from many companies wishing to partner with us so WATCH THIS SPACE in 2018 because we're only going to get BIGGER and BETTER :)

None of this is possible without the amazing volunteers who work in the background to get these events set up! We are always looking for more volunteers to support us, so if you want to get involved in working for an active and vibrant community please contact one of the admins! 

Alternatively join our private members group and post a message there or join our Slack channel! 

Private Members Group: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/intertechlgbt/" rel="nofollow"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/groups/intertechlgbt/&lt;/a&gt;

Slack Channel: &lt;a href="https://intertechdo.signup.team/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow" data-lynx-uri="https://l.facebook.com/l.php?u=https%3A%2F%2Fintertechdo.signup.team%2F&amp;amp;h=ATOpjsvh5VpMLoPiafw1c9dq_p62xboDA4N52-kZs6TiXQxetzkTeFUFOxQXvm9GSrnLaYtB3w2siiLbOHYa2bNxmSPZmx0cbe7ipjD6kejRKZ1ZYCmEpLrpXHSkhvl7ITH75gNTG2ma4Sb6RuU9Ks0QwcpdCT3eZ8HcJO_XLpj3YMY" data-lynx-mode="origin"&gt;http://slack.intertechlgbt.com/&lt;/a&gt;

Hope to see many of you there! 

xoxo

Jerry@InterTech LGBT+ Diversity Forum</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 13:42:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/35655</guid><title>InterTech @ MozFest House - Digital Inclusion</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/35655</link><description>&lt;b&gt;InterTech &amp; Mozilla Festival&lt;/b&gt; invite you to a networking event as part of&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href="https://mozillafestival.org/"&gt;MozFest 2017&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;

Mozilla is fueling the movement to ensure the Internet is a global public resource, open and accessible to all. The Internet's role in &lt;b&gt;economic opportunity, creativity, personal connection, free expression and democracy&lt;/b&gt; around the world has made it a fundamental part of our modern lives. Yet today, censorship, surveillance, walled gardens and apathy are putting the open Internet at risk.

Join us in a safe space to &lt;b&gt;meet up, network and build the vital connections we need &lt;/b&gt;to ensure we can work together to build a more open, respectful and inclusive web for everyone.

Join us for an evening at the &lt;b&gt;Royal Society of Arts&lt;/b&gt;, as part of the &lt;b&gt;MozFest House &lt;/b&gt;week of programming, see the &lt;a href="https://mozillafestival.org/house"&gt;entire programme online&lt;/a&gt;, to hear from speakers on the subject of &lt;b&gt;digital inclusion&lt;/b&gt;; one of the major spaces in MozFest this year. The focus of the talks will be to promote ways we can &lt;b&gt;develop and promote safe spaces&lt;/b&gt; on the internet which we hope will fuel the discussion for the rest of the evening.

If you'd like to attend &lt;b&gt;please sign-up on the link below&lt;/b&gt; and take advantage of this incredible opportunity to network and learn from one another.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 13:28:01 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/35153</guid><title>InterTech @ BBC News - Embracing Change</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/35153</link><description>InterTech and BBC News invite you to their &lt;b&gt;speaker event &lt;/b&gt;to hear about how they&#x2019;re embracing change in the &lt;b&gt;ever-changing world of development and diversity &amp; inclusion&lt;/b&gt;. 

The evening will feature speakers from different disciplines discussing how change has impacted them and what they&#x2019;ve done to adapt as well as how the BBC are tackling LGBT, diversity &amp; inclusivity. 

Following the speeches, there will be an &lt;b&gt;opportunity to network with BBC News Design &amp; Engineering staff &lt;/b&gt;and guests before continuing the evening in a nearby venue.

Please signup using the link below and take note of the requirements around security.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 15:53:13 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/31459</guid><title>InterTech @ Goldman Sachs - Let&#x2019;s talk about FinTech</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/31459</link><description>InterTech and &lt;b&gt;Goldman Sachs&lt;/b&gt; invite you to the third joint speaker event to hear how our LGBT network members in the Goldman Sachs Engineering Division are:

&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Using &lt;b&gt;machine learning to profile our traders&#x2019; behaviour &lt;/b&gt;to identify patterns and anomalies;

&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Using natural language processing in &lt;b&gt;Chat Bots to help our traders&lt;/b&gt; efficiently find solutions to common problems from their desktop.

&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;Following the speech there will be an opportunity to network with other members and guests.

&lt;b&gt;Spaces are limited and will be allocated on a first-come, first-served basis &lt;/b&gt;so please do register using the link below.

Please bring your event sign-up confirmation on the day, along with some form of ID showing your name.

For more information on tech at Goldman Sachs, visit &lt;a href="http://gs.com/engineering" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow"&gt;gs.com/engineering&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 13:53:02 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/30889</guid><title>InterTech &amp; The IoD - Pride in Business</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/30889</link><description>&lt;b&gt;An announcement...&lt;/b&gt;

We're delighted to share with you the exciting news that &lt;b&gt;InterTech has aligned with 'The IoD'&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt; (The Institute of Directors)&lt;/b&gt; to support&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;LGBTQ+ business leaders to network, share information and stories and do business with like-minded individuals. InterTech, working alongside&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.techlondonadvocates.org.uk/"&gt;TechLondonAdvocates&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://seriesq.com/"&gt;Series Q&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;and the &lt;a href="http://www.gwn.org.uk/"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Gay Women&#x2019;s Network&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; all sit on the IoD Pride in Business committee supporting the IoD's Royal Charter of 1906 to support its members.

&lt;b&gt;An invitation...&lt;/b&gt;

Following on from the hugely popular &lt;a href="https://www.iod.com/news-campaigns/news/articles/116-Pall-Mall-decked-in-rainbows-for-Pride-in-Business-launch"&gt;Pride in Business&lt;/a&gt; launch in July tickets are now available for this months event where the &lt;b&gt;Rt Hon John Bercow MP, speaker of the House of Commons&lt;/b&gt;, will join us for a talk covering his extraordinary range of views on politics today and efforts to reinvigorate Parliament, as well as being a vocal and visible ally to LGBTQ+ people globally.

Following the talk, there will be an opportunity for networking over drinks and canap&#xE9;s.

If you'd like to attend then please follow the links below to register&lt;b&gt;*&lt;/b&gt; both with the IoD and for the event. We look forward to seeing InterTech members at the second of our many 'IoD Pride in Business' events going forward.

&lt;b&gt;*You must register for this event; those turning up without registration will not be permitted entry due to the nature of the venue and capacity. On that note please ensure any guests you wish to bring are registered or recorded as a delegate under your registration.&lt;/b&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 12:35:08 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/25791</guid><title>InterTech @ Capco</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/25791</link><description>Capco invites InterTech members to join them for an &lt;b &gt;informal networking session&lt;/b&gt; at their offices in the City. 

Capco are a consulting firm focused solely on the&lt;b&gt; financial services industry&lt;/b&gt;; and during the evening we will hear briefly from Capco Digital, the fastest growing area in Capco as well as the Capco LGBT Team and the events they will be hosting for the remainder of the year.

This will be a great opportunity for people to &lt;b&gt;learn more about what Capco and Capco Digital do and see old and new InterTech faces&lt;/b&gt; once again!

Please do sign up on the link below as there is limited capacity and your names are needed for the evening's access.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 10:55:27 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/25660</guid><title>Our Summer Retrospective...</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/25660</link><description>Please join us for our summer and post-pride season&lt;b&gt; InterTech LGBT+ Forum retrospective&lt;/b&gt;.

This will be a chance for you, our members, to join us in &lt;b&gt;reflecting on what we've done&lt;/b&gt; over the summer period and &lt;b&gt;help shape what we take forward&lt;/b&gt; for the rest of the year.

So come prepared with your thoughts, actions, and views and we'll have plenty of post-it notes, markers and paper available for the evening.

We're kindly being &lt;b&gt;hosted in Capgemini's office who will be providing soft drinks and nibbles&lt;/b&gt; for the session.

&lt;em&gt;Please do ensure to register for the session as we require your names to be provided to Capgemini for entry to the building.&lt;/em&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 17:18:07 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/18784</guid><title>Salesforce &amp; InterTech Pride Celebration</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/18784</link><description>We're excited to be invited to join &lt;b&gt;Salesforce &lt;/b&gt;for their Pride in London celebrations at Archer Street Bar, taking place just minutes away from Piccadilly Circus, a perfect spot to watch the parade.

It&#x2019;s time to &lt;b&gt;come together and celebrate diversity&lt;/b&gt;, whether you're a member of InterTech, Salesforce, the LGBTQ community, a straight ally or anyone else - you're welcome.

Following the parade, those marching with InterTech will re-unite with us further celebrations and to continue to party into the evening.

We have &lt;b&gt;12 tables reserved&lt;/b&gt; outside of Archer Street and an area inside reserved too; use of the venue's facilities and what promises to be an entertaining day with performances, on &lt;b&gt;Archer Street Bar's very own stage&lt;/b&gt;, from great names in the West End and more.

&lt;b&gt;Spaces are limited so please only register is you are certain you can attend. &lt;/b&gt;

Wristbands for the bar and food will only be issued to those who have registered online.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 13:00:46 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/17810</guid><title>The "Pride in Business" Reception</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/17810</link><description>The IoD will mark the launch of the &#x2018;Pride in Business Network&#x2019; amongst its membership with a drinks reception on the evening of July 7th, the eve of London&#x2019;s famous Gay Pride March, at the IoD&#x2019;s Headquarters on Pall Mall.

With LGBTQ+ entrepreneurs and business leaders now making waves in the business world, the IoD has partnered with other groups &#x2013; InterTech, TechLondonAdvocates, Series Q and the Gay Women&#x2019;s Network &#x2013; to celebrate their achievements on this most festive of weekends.

The drinks will mark the beginning of the IoD&#x2019;s Pride in Business series of networking events and mentoring, more details of which will be forthcoming in due course.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 21:25:12 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/17809</guid><title>Google &amp; InterTech Pre-Pride Quiz</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/17809</link><description>It's back! The highly anticipated Pre-Pride Quiz with Google and InterTech!

Join us at the Google Central St. Giles offices near Tottenham Court Road for an evening of quizzing, networking, and pre-pride celebrations.

We're delighted to have our famous InterTech quizmaster Tim Macavoy back once again to guide us through the evening - we're excited to see you at what promises to be the best Pre-Pride quiz yet.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 21:18:07 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/17808</guid><title>InterTech @ Pride in London 2017</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/17808</link><description>It's that time of year again and we're so excited to be taking part in the &lt;b&gt;Pride in London &lt;/b&gt;parade thanks to our wonderful sponsors over at &lt;b&gt;Salesforce&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;TripAdvisor &amp;amp; Accenture.&lt;/b&gt;

We only have a &lt;b&gt;small number of tickets&lt;/b&gt; for the parade this year, but that doesn't mean we don't want you to make any less noise or party atmosphere than previously. As ever we've t-shirts and goody bags so we'd love for you to come along, join the parade and celebrate one of our biggest events of the year with InterTech and friends.

Please &lt;b&gt;only sign up if you are certain you will take part in the parade&lt;/b&gt;; we'd hate for someone to not be able to take part because a ticket has been assigned to someone who isn't going to come along.

If you're not able to get a ticket or instead want to watch the parade then sign-up for our &lt;b&gt;Pride Party with Salesforce&lt;/b&gt; where we've plenty of availability and would be delighted to see you.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 21:06:13 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/17807</guid><title>Bloomberg: Raising Awareness on Bisexuality</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/17807</link><description>The LGBT &amp;amp; Ally Community at Bloomberg, in partnership with Citi and State Street, invite InterTech members to join an intimate discussion on bisexuality to help raise awareness on what it means to be bisexual and to discuss some of the major prejudice, stigma and discrimination faced by the bisexual community.

&lt;i&gt;Bloomberg have invited several panellists from the LGBT community, who will help to demystify common preconceptions about bisexuality. They will also explore the stigmas associated to bisexual men and women in society and share their personal experiences. This event will offer the audience an opportunity to ask questions about bisexuality that they may not have had the chance to ask before.&lt;/i&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 20:59:38 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/17253</guid><title>Palantir LGBT Pride Speakers Event: Being Out At Work</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/17253</link><description>Palantir have invited Intertech to their LGBT Pride Speakers event which will be followed by snacks and drinks! Registration is required so please follow the link below.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 19:46:16 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/17252</guid><title>A world of pure IMAGINATION</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/17252</link><description>Who says nothing happens after Pride season?!

Imagination would like to invite Intertech members to a grand tour of their central London offices followed by nibbles and drinks! Please note that there are limited tickets so please sign up early to avoid disappointment!

&lt;b&gt;Itinerary&lt;/b&gt;

6pm - Arrival and networking drinks

7pm - Imagination + Imagination Labs introduction

7:15pm - Imagination Labs demonstration

7:45/8pm - Return to Atrium

9pm to End - More drinks and networking over the road at the pub</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 19:42:03 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/16451</guid><title>Pre-Pride Networking (+ping pong!) -- NOW FULL</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/16451</link><description>&lt;i&gt;Sorry! Tickets are now sold out for the event. &lt;/i&gt;

&lt;i&gt;

&lt;/i&gt;

InterTech &amp;amp; Microsoft would like to invite you to a special networking (and ping-pong!) evening to kick off the Pride in London season. 

We have secured a private room at Bounce Farringdon (nearest tube: Chancery Lane) from 6.30pm til late. We'll have exclusive use of the ping pong tables in this room and a limited free bar! We'll have a brief hello from Microsoft's International Director of Diversity &amp;amp; Inclusion and we hope to share more about our plans for the InterTech parade walking group. 

&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Please note that registration is mandatory for this event.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 15:50:06 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/13137</guid><title>InterTech Mentoring Update</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/13137</link><description>Following previous efforts to develop a mentoring platform, we revisited the idea in our January Co-Creation event. The output from the event was a sketch of a mentoring scheme aiming to enable our members better connect and share experiences. 

Since then, Colin, one of our members, has been working with &lt;a href="http://www.werkinapp.com/"&gt;WERKIN&lt;/a&gt;, which is led by an LGBT+ entrepreneur, to make this a reality and we're delighted to say we&#x2019;re now ready to run a trial of "InterTech mentoring&#x201D; to gauge interest and assess the potential value to the community. Participants will have access to a mobile app designed to make mentoring more time efficient and productive, particularly where mentor and mentees span companies and locations. 

&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Are you interested? &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt; We would appreciate you filling in your details &lt;a href="https://werkin.typeform.com/to/XQDaj8"&gt;on this Typeform&lt;/a&gt; (7 questions only, promise!) to understand what you would hope to get out of a mentoring relationship. We'll then feed back once we've heard from everyone who's interested.

&lt;i&gt;Editor's note: In this beta stage the organisers have created an iOS compatible app only. We will share news of other platforms soon. &lt;/i&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 08:31:13 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/8958</guid><title>Global LGBTIQ Human Rights in the Populist Era; Fundraiser with OutRight Action International</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/8958</link><description>The increasingly isolationist policies of the UK, US and other Western powers have wrought severe repercussions on the global LGBTIQ community. Earlier this month, an emboldened Russia rounded up and tortured over 100 gay men. Late last year, the President of Gambia vowed to personally slit the throats of gay Gambians. And closer to home, hate crimes against LGBTIQ people are on the rise.

Please join the London Young Professionals Engagement Committee as we host Jessica Stern, the Executive Director of OutRight Action International, for a discussion on the future of LGBTIQ human rights - at home and abroad - as we enter this new populist era. Jessica will be joined by two grassroots activists who will highlight the challenges they face fighting for the LGBTIQ community in their home countries, as well as the role that the international community can play in supporting them.

The evening will kick off at 7pm with an hour of unlimited Pimm's for all guests. Come by for a drink before heading out for the evening, meet like-minded professionals and students, and learn what you can do to support LGBTIQ human rights at home and abroad. 100% of your &#xA3;15 entry goes directly to OutRight Action International, the world's leading LGBTIQ human rights charity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 10:50:38 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/8646</guid><title>InterTech Social - Thursday 4th May</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/8646</link><description>Following the success of our March social (with over 250 of you lovelies in attendence!)... we bring you 2017 social number 2! For the May social, we will be moving to the much cooler, much cheaper location of Big Chill Bar on Brick Lane (yes - East London!). 

Look forward to seeing everyone there!</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 09:39:29 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/5505</guid><title>Student Pride</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/5505</link><description>We were proud to be part of the National Student Pride event on 25th February! Thank you to everyone who came to meet us and to our wonderful volunteers for giving their time and energy to the event!&#xD;
&#xD;
&lt;a href="http://www.studentpride.co.uk"&gt;National Student Pride&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 23:35:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/4706</guid><title>The life and death of Alan Turing</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/4706</link><description>InterTech members have been invited to join Bloomberg's LGBT &amp; Ally Community for this exclusive event featuring our guest speaker, acclaimed author, Andrew Hodges, who will focus his talk on Alan Turing.&#xD;
 &#xD;
 In his short life, the British mathematician Alan Turing became the founder of modern computer science and the leading scientific figure in the Allied breaking of German ciphers in World War 2. He was also a gay man who was prosecuted under the British criminal law in 1952.&#xD;
 &#xD;
 Andrew Hodges will describe the connection between these aspects of Alan Turing&#x2019;s life and the background to his death in 1954.&#xD;
 &#xD;
 Registration for this event is mandatory. Please ensure you enter your full details in the registration panel on the right hand side of this page. You will receive a confirmation email if your registration details are received.&#xD;
 &#xD;
 Light snacks and drinks will be served on arrival.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 11:13:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/4499</guid><title>InterTech&#xA0;Social: Thurs 2nd March</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/4499</link><description>Following January's kick off event, our first InterTech member-organised Social of 2017 will be on the Thursday 2nd March.&#xD;
 &#xD;
 Givent the number of people who have signed up, we have moved the location to the Courthouse hotel where we held our summer event.&#xD;
     &#xD;
     Please sign up via the Eventbrite link - we look forward to seeing you there!</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 07:19:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/4493</guid><title>LGBT History Month Event: Stand Up - for LGBT Rights @ Visa</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/4493</link><description>Our friends at Visa are marking LGBT History Month with a &lt;b&gt;comedy night&lt;/b&gt; and would like to extend an invitation to all InterTech members. Hosted by Chris Fitchew, the event will include three stars of stage and screen:&#xD;
 &#xD;
 &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stephen K Amos from Live at the Apollo, 11 O&#x2019;clock Show, and Celebrity Juice&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zoe Lyons from Live at the Apollo, Comedy Central and Mock the Week&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chris Neill from Radio 4 and Radio 2&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;The evening will start at 17:30 with a networking reception. The show starts at 19:00. There will be a bar to purchase food and drink but the show is free.&#xD;
 &#xD;
 &lt;b&gt;Please note - you will need to have registered in advance to attend this event.&lt;/b&gt; Registration will close on 14 Feb.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 19:09:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/3923</guid><title>The 2017 Co-Creation Event</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/3923</link><description>Thanks to the InterTech Community, 2016 was a hugely successful year with a large number of community driven events being held. On top of this, our participation at Pride in London was the largest yet.&#xD;
   &#xD;
   In 2017 we would like to deliver even more, and we need your help...&#xD;
   &#xD;
   We would like to open up InterTech, tapping into the enthusiasm and creativity of our community - and allowing each and every member to feel empowered to lead, create and organise their own events or socials. &lt;b&gt;By the community, for the community.&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
   &#xD;
   On the 12th Jan, we invite you to join us at BCG Digital Ventures (who have kindly offered us a room to run our co-creation session), to generate ideas and form teams. The evening will go as follows:&#xD;
     &#xD;
     18:45 - 19:00	Introduction&#xD;
     19:00 - 20:00	Ideation and Team Discussion&#xD;
     20:15 - 20:30	Q&amp;amp;A and Lessons Learnt&#xD;
     20:30 - Late	To the pub (We have booked an area at Archer Street W1D 7AP)&#xD;
     &#xD;
  &lt;b&gt;   If you'd like to come to the Co-Creation event, please make sure you &lt;a href="https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/intertech-2017-co-creation-event-tickets-30961240905"&gt;sign up via EventBrite&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/b&gt; As with all of our community events, there's no charge.&#xD;
     &#xD;
     If you cannot make it to the Co-Creation Event but want to join us at the pub, please feel free to join us later.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 11:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/2955</guid><title>The Minimum Viable Diversity Pledge</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/2955</link><description>InterTech is pleased to be supporting the Minimum Viable Diversity Pledge. We strongly support increased diversity in the tech sector and encourage all efforts that contribute to this goal.&#xD;
   &#xD;
   &lt;a href="http://minimumviablediversitypledge.com"&gt;http://minimumviablediversitypledge.com&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 14:58:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/2954</guid><title>InterTech + Facebook Hack - come and see the judging!</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/2954</link><description>This weekend, techies, project managers and designers are getting together at Facebook HQ for our 4th #MakeItBetter hackathon. If you'd like to join us to see the results, sign up now for a 'supporter' ticket. &#xD;
&#xD;
Hurry though as we'll be closing registration later this evening!</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 14:51:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/2952</guid><title>Stonewall Season event @ Visa</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/2952</link><description>This year marks the first Stonewall Season - and our friends at &lt;b&gt;Visa&lt;/b&gt; would like to extend an invitation for InterTech Members to join them at their celebratory event on 8th November. &#xD;
 &#xD;
 Speakers include Pip Bunce from Credit Suisse and Ruth Hunt, Stonewall CEO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 13:54:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/2953</guid><title>Transgender Day of Remembrance</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/2953</link><description>Transgender Day of Remembrance (TDOR) is an annual observance held November 20 that honours the memory of those whose lives were lost in acts of anti-transgender violence. &#xD;
 &#xD;
 To mark this event, Barclays Spectrum, the staff led LGBT network for Barclays employees, and Cleary Gottlieb Steen &amp; Hamilton, a leading international law firm are hosting an evening in support of Mermaids UK, a charity that supports children or young people up to 19 years old suffering from gender identity issues and their families.</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 14:00:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/2721</guid><title>Make stuff better - Facebook + InterTech 24hr Hackathon (iv)</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/2721</link><description>Facebook and InterTech are teaming up for another continuous 24 hour Hack from &lt;i&gt;Saturday 5 Nov at 11:00 through till  Sunday 6 Nov at 13:00.&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
   &#xD;
   Bring your skills, your laptop and energy and come participate in Europe's biggest LGBT+ Hackathon!  Our theme, again is &lt;b&gt;#MakeStuffBetter&lt;/b&gt;, like years before we have created some amazing products. How will you make stuff better? How can you spread tolerance, promote health, or create awareness?&#xD;
   &#xD;
   We will get together at Facebook's amazing offices to hear new ideas, and bring all of our design, technical and organisational talents together over 24 hours to make a change in the world! This is a chance to meet others, and do something good for the broader LGBT+ community and share your tech skills (not a place to form your startup!).&#xD;
   &#xD;
   For the 24 hour hack our participants will be ideas people with their concept on how to make stuff better, developers, UX, content and visual designers, along with a smattering of talented tech project managers / coordinators.&#xD;
   &#xD;
   There are &lt;b&gt;supporter&lt;/b&gt; tickets available for those who just wish to cheer on the good efforts and see the eventual products and prizes at the end of the hack -  &lt;i&gt;Supporter times:&lt;/i&gt; &lt;i&gt;10:30am-12:30 on Sunday 6th November.&lt;/i&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 21:24:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/2718</guid><title>InterTech Meet with IHS Markit</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/2718</link><description>IHS Markit Pride in partnership with InterTech invite you to join us at the Water Poet, Spitalfields on &lt;b&gt;Wednesday 26th October from 6pm&lt;/b&gt;. Come and join other InterTech members for this informal meetup. There will be some food and a few mini challenges to take part in.&#xD;
  &#xD;
  &lt;i&gt;IHS Markit bring together the deepest intelligence across the widest set of capital-intensive industries and markets. By connecting data across variables, our analysts and industry specialists present our customers with a richer, highly integrated view of their world. &lt;/i&gt;&#xD;
  &#xD;
  &lt;i&gt;We are a dynamic team that includes more than 5,000 analysts, data scientists, financial experts and industry specialists. Our global information expertise spans numerous industries, including leading positions in finance, energy and transportation. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="http://l.facebook.com/l.php?u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ihsmarkit.com%2F&amp;amp;h=7AQERYrv4&amp;amp;enc=AZOpft8fAFo3Qj4kxxTVgEL_MF_sR7Q29pUjTGONkF1Qxb3Y-pr_zRhza8Avqer_Pdc&amp;amp;s=1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow nofollow"&gt;&lt;i&gt;http://www.ihsmarkit.com/&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 13:58:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/2634</guid><title>Stonewall Season</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/2634</link><description>Stonewall Season is a national festival celebrating lesbian, gay, bi &amp;amp; trans life and culture. From 1st-10th November, events will be hosted throughout Great Britain, many of them close to home in London. &#xD;
&#xD;
We're looking forward to sharing some awesome events with you - for now check out &lt;a href="http://www.stonewallseason.org.uk/"&gt;stonewallseason.org.uk&lt;/a&gt; for details. </description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 21:11:22 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/2633</guid><title>Facebook Hack is Back!</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/2633</link><description>We're back at Facebook HQ in Euston for another amazing 24hr hack! &#xD;
  &#xD;
  This will be our 4th hackathon at Facebook, and once again we're brining InterTech'ers together for 24 hours to &lt;b&gt;#MakeStuffBetter&lt;/b&gt;&#xD;
  &#xD;
  The date to remember is the &lt;b&gt;5th November &lt;/b&gt;(...and the 6th) - keep your diaries clear and we'll send you an update on the signup details very shortly. &#xD;
 &#xD;
 &lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Registration opening shortly&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 20:59:04 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/2632</guid><title>InterTech Social with MVF Global</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/2632</link><description>MVF Global (a tech start up in the customer acquisition space) have recently refurbished their new bar and cafe area and have kindly invited Intertech to come and have pizza/beer/non-alcoholic beverages on them! They are a fast growing start up and are keen to meet some like minded people who are:&#xD;
&#xD;
1. Up for sharing pizza/beer/non-alcoholic beverages with them and have a great time. (Lets face it, based on past experience it will inevitably end with everyone going out in Soho)&#xD;
&#xD;
2. Looking for marketing, data science, and programming roles in a start up environment&#xD;
&#xD;
It has been while since we did something so this would be an amazing opportunity to see some old faces and new!</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 20:50:54 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/1808</guid><title>Informal InterTech Meetup</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/1808</link><description>Come and join other InterTech members for this informal meetup at Ku Bar on Frith Street. &#xD;
  &#xD;
  Please join us on Ku's upper floor from 7.30pm this Wednesday.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 06:32:55 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/1635</guid><title>Queer Theory for Queer Times</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/1635</link><description>Join ThoughtWorks and InterTech in our Soho office on the 9th of August for a fireside discussion and networking with Joe Parslow: PhD Candidate; Visiting Lecturer at the Royal Central School of Speech and Drama; cabaret producer; and drag queen&#x2019;s helping hand. Joe will be exploring the theme of building communities, specifically queer communities, as he takes us through a potted history of queer thinking to consider what queer might mean today, what it can do, and how we might use it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2016 09:32:23 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/1338</guid><title>InterTech @ Pride London</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/1338</link><description>InterTech smashed it at Pride in London last month. Our 200 strong walking group must have been the loudest in the parade. A big thank-you to everyone who marched and represented the LGBT community in the tech industry. There are more photos in our Facebook group &lt;a href="https://facebook.com/groups/intertechlgbt/"&gt;facebook.com/groups/intertechlgbt/&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 12:46:38 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/1337</guid><title>Film Screening with director Jake Graf</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/1337</link><description>InterTech and Softwire have arranged an evening with award winning actor/director Jake Graf showcasing Chance and Dawn, two of his recent short films. The screening is hosted by Softwire in their Camden offices and will be followed by a question and answer session with Jake and Kat Holmes, the producer of Dawn.&lt;br &gt;&lt;br &gt;This event is free to attend but we will be collecting donations on the night, which will go directly to fund the cost of Dawn, which was almost entirely self-funded. The suggested donations are &#xA3;10 for members, &#xA3;5 for students.&#xD;
&#xD;
Space is limited so please book!</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 12:19:27 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/926</guid><title>Join InterTech @ Pride 2016</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/926</link><description>InterTech represents the vibrant LGBT community in the UK tech and startup industry. This year we're back at London Pride, thanks to our fantastic sponsors Salesforce, Cisco, Medallia, Accenture, ThoughtWorks, TripAdvisor, Google and King.&#xD;
  &#xD;
  Due to new Pride rules, we are limited to 200 InterTech members in the march this year. However, we've got lots of t-shirts and goody bags, so we're inviting all members, friends and supporters to come along, collect your free goody bag and t-shirt and cheer us on. If there are extra spaces available on the day, you'll be welcome to join the parade.&#xD;
    &#xD;
  Looking forward to seeing you all there!</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 09:32:22 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/1141</guid><title>We stand with Orlando</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/1141</link><description>Sending love to our brothers and sisters in Orlando x</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2016 08:38:32 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/1096</guid><title>PRIDE: Talk - The Power of Participation</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/1096</link><description>InterTech members have been invited to join the Cisco LGBT and Ally network for an evening of discussion about "The Power of Participation". &#xD;
  &#xD;
  Diversity Role Models' patron and former NBA basketball player, &lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.johnamaechi.com/" rel="nofollow"&gt;John Amaechi&lt;/a&gt;, will share his personal story of struggle and triumph and his perspective on the power of positive role models in sport and business. John works closely with Amnesty International on LGBT rights and often acts as a spokesperson on these issues. Dedicated to ensuring that the world of sport operates within a human rights ethos, John will illustrate that despite what we are often told, &#x201C;&lt;em&gt;the most unlikely of people, in the most improbable of circumstances can become extraordinary &#x2013; but to achieve this, we must be our authentic selves."&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;
      &#xD;
    We will also be joined by American fitness expert and TV host, &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pavelka.co.uk/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Jessie Pavelka&lt;/a&gt;, who will share his thoughts on the power of role models in health and wellbeing. &#xD;
      &#xD;
    But that&#x2019;s not all &#x2013; stay for drinks and canap&#xE9;s to continue the conversation with your peers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 10:00:49 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/924</guid><title>Pride Breakfast</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/924</link><description>InterTech, InterMedia and RoyaLGBT &amp; Friends, the LGBT+ employee network of King, are hosting a pre-Pride celebration in King's very own magical Kingdom. We promise drinks, food and one of London&#x2019;s top DJs. Pretty much the perfect Pride warm-up.&#xD;
      &#xD;
    This is the hottest Pride ticket in town and spaces are limited, so book your ticket quickly!&#xD;
    &#xD;
    After the breakfast we'll be heading over to Portland Place to take part in the parade. Be sure to register for a place in our walking group in order to nab your very own t-shirt and goodie bag.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 08:42:52 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/864</guid><title>Pre-Pride Quiz and Networking Evening</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/864</link><description>Join InterTech and Google at their amazing Central St. Giles office near Tottenham Court Road for a night of quiz action and networking. We have our very own InterTech royalty &lt;b&gt;Tim Macavoy &lt;/b&gt;as the host with the most. Kick off your Pride season in style!</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 10:50:09 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/825</guid><title>A reminder to join the InterTech Facebook group</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/825</link><description>One of the things we've always been keen to do is create a space where members of the LGBT+ tech community can openly network, forge connections and support one another. Live events are great for this, but not everyone can make them, so we're going to give a facebook Group a try.&#xD;
     &#xD;
 The  group is a place to share stories about LGBT+ and tech. It's a place to ask questions about your career or seek out other members who might be able to assist in it. It's a place to post job vacancies or seek freelancers or promote your services to the community. It's a place to arrange socials and generally be a bit silly and have a bit of fun.&#xD;
     &#xD;
 Who knows how it will evolve. They key thing is that we all share a common bond, so introduce yourself, support one another and play nicely!&#xD;
     &#xD;
   &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/intertechlgbt/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/groups/intertechlgbt/&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 09:42:37 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/671</guid><title>General Events Structure</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/671</link><description>For the last couple of years, we have broadly had 3 types of InterTech Event:&#xD;
  &#xD;
  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;InterTech:DO - &lt;em&gt;A chance to volunteer your skills and time to develop coll tech projects to make stuff better. For the past year the teams have been developing a mentoring platform. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;InterTech:TALK - &lt;em&gt;A networking event with a lecture session on a topic relevant to the LGBT+ Tech community. Typically sponsored by a company. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;InterTech:MEET - &lt;em&gt;A social/networking event with a fun element (ping pong and console gaming sessions for example).&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;We are temporarily suspending this structure for now. We hope to start again later in the year. If you want to get involved and develop any of these strands (or a type we haven't thought of yet) please &lt;a href="mailto:info@intertechlgbt.com" target="_blank"&gt;get in touch.&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 10:03:46 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/767</guid><title>A call for London Pride sponsors</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/767</link><description>Want to help with our Pride celebrations this year? Get your company involved by sponsoring the best walking group in the parade! We're expecting a 200+ strong walking group this year containing some of the finest talent in the UK tech sector.&#xD;
   &#xD;
   To hear more about our plans and how you can get involved, email &lt;b&gt;info@intertechlgbt.com.&lt;/b&gt; &#xD;
 &#xD;
 Additionally, if you'd like to donate some time to help team InterTech with the planning, or some kit to include in our Pride swag bags, get in touch!</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 18:00:47 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/842</guid><title>InterTech May social meetup</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/842</link><description>Following on from the success of last month's social meetup, we're doing the same again in May. Everyone is invited, so come along and meet some new people. We're keeping it incredibly informal, so feel free to come and go as you please.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 08:37:14 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/670</guid><title>Community-Run Events</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/670</link><description>Over the next few months we will invite InterTech members to create events, whether an informal social/networking event or perhaps an event run by an employer's LGBT network group and open to InterTech members. We will soon be creating a Facebook Group in which everyone can discuss what's next. In the meantime we are using the existing &lt;a href="http://intertechlgbt.us9.list-manage.com/track/click?u=8f58d5ef44e4a856353bbc2b3&amp;id=23d30c9039&amp;e=056e0c78c4" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook Page&lt;/a&gt; to promote these events.&#xD;
  &#xD;
  InterTech Member &lt;em&gt;Rob Farthing &lt;/em&gt;has created the first informal event and advertised it on the Facebook Page. If you want to set up an event with us, &lt;a href="mailto:info@intertechlgbt.com" target="_blank"&gt;drop us a mail.&lt;/a&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 09:56:42 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/654</guid><title>InterTech:DO Equinox</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/654</link><description>Thursday 24th saw the last in the current series of InterTech:DO events, held in Soho. We made further progress with the MentorMe platform, as well as focusing on how to better communicate with InterTech members via Facebook and email. A big thank you to all those that attended, and to ThoughtWorks for putting us up.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 09:35:03 +0100</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/665</guid><title>InterTech:DO MentorMe Hack</title><link>https://intertechlgbt.interests.me/story/665</link><description>What happened the last time Intertech got together at Campus, a Google space to work on the MentorMe platform? &#xD;
&#xD;
We had many ideas, some disruptive, some worth gold, and all them discussed! Finalisation of all the page flows, and being *THIS* close to getting over the last technical hurdles to get a working page/linked-in working in Node.js&#xD;
&#xD;
We also managed to get some great feedback from several of the participants on how a few changes could really help streamline the next session. &#xD;
&#xD;
Many thanks for all the contributions and conversations! </description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 13:32:41 +0100</pubDate></item></channel></rss>